JOSHUA ANDY OPOTE

Contact

Address:

Nairobi ,Kenya

Phone:

+254 790 552 354

Email:

Joshandy2021@gmail.com

Github:

Andy3643

Behance:

Joshua Andy

Languages

English Kiswahili

Summary

I am a talented software engineer with a vast understanding of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Python. With an understanding of these three languages with various frameworks associated with them, I can develop full-stack websites and I'm also free to learn new technologies. Having worked on various projects during my studies and freelancing career, I intend to make the world a better place through code.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Imaginative Thinking
- Complex problem solver
- Teamwork
- Creative eye for design
- Front-end web development

Experience

06/2022 to 12/2022

Freelance Web Designer

- **Upwork and Fiver**, Nairobi
 - Completing assignments for online clients.
 - Designing apps with flask, Django, and angular.
 - Consuming APIs with python
 - Data analytics with excel
 - Completing UX/UI projects for clients.

02/2022 to 12/2022

Graphic Designer GEVIC MUNDARE SUPPLIES, Nairobi

- Logo design
- Designing posters and flyers.
- Branding

01/2021 to 12/2022

Graphic Designer

STBC Adventures and Safaris, Nairobi

- Logo design
- Designing posters and flyers.
- Branding
- Making social media flyers for advertisement

Computer Skills

- HTML 5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Front-end web development with Angular and React
- Python
- Flask
- Django
- MySQL

Freelance Graphic Designer

FREELANCE, Nairobi

- Designing logos for clients.
- Designing posters and flyers for businesses.
- Branding
- Creating web content and photo editing.

Education

2022

Software Development: Moringa School – Distinction

2020

Bachelor of Science: Kenyatta University – Second class upper

2015

Computer applications and Microsoft Packages:

Christian Computer Technology Center – Distinction

2014

KCSE: Nyang'ori High School - A-

Additional Training

2022

Product Design Bootcamp: Microsoft – Product market research, product definition, design planning, user testing, user persona creation.

2022

UX &UI Bootcamp: The East African University (TEAU)— Figma design, prototype modeling, creating user personas, research

Referees

Gideon Onsongo,

Associate,

Gevic Mundare Supplies.

0723 742 975.

Boniface Mirikwa,

CEO,

STBC Adventures and

Safaris.

0710 164 192.